[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ I met a gin-soaked
barroom queen in Memphis ♪
♪ She tried to take me
upstairs for a ride ♪
♪ She had to heave me
right across her shoulder ♪
♪ 'Cause I just can't seem to
drink you off my mind ♪
♪ It's the honky tonk women ♪
♪ That gimme, gimme, gimme
the honky tonk blues ♪
♪ I laid a divorcee
in New York City ♪
♪ I had to put up some
kind of a fight ♪
♪ The lady, then she
covered me in roses ♪
♪ She blew my nose
and then she blew my mind ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
♪ It's the honky tonk women ♪
♪ That gimme, gimme, gimme
the honky tonk blues ♪
♪ Yeah, alright! ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]
♪ It's the honky tonk women
- (Honky tonk) ♪
♪ That gimme, gimme, gimme
the honky tonk blues ♪
♪ It's the honky tonk women
- (Honky tonk) ♪
♪ That gimme, gimme, gimme
the honky tonk blues ♪
♪ Woo! ♪